{
    "subject": "resource/John_F._Kennedy",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Filmed_assassinations",
    "human_readable": "The subject of John F. Kennedy is Filmmed assassinations.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.811038613319397,
            "question": "Was the assassination of John F. Kennedy filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7516400814056396,
            "question": "Are there any films depicting the assassination of John F. Kennedy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7079280018806458,
            "question": "How have film depictions influenced public perception of John F. Kennedy's assassination?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.510187029838562,
            "question": "What event is associated with John F. Kennedy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44149842858314514,
            "question": "Have any documentaries explored the role of film in understanding John F. Kennedy's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42644819617271423,
            "question": "What historical significance do film recordings have regarding John F. Kennedy's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4062589108943939,
            "question": "How was John F. Kennedy's death captured?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3869209289550781,
            "question": "What is the impact of visual media on historical events like the assassination of John F. Kennedy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2671496272087097,
            "question": "What ethical considerations surround the filming and distribution of an assassination?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2009958177804947,
            "question": "What type of footage exists related to John F. Kennedy?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of John F. Kennedy is Filmmed assassinations.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6868_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What ethical considerations surround the filming and distribution of an assassination?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6868_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the impact of visual media on historical events like the assassination of John F. Kennedy?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6868_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How was John F. Kennedy's death captured?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6868_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6868_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6868_122.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6868_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6868_126.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6868_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6868_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6868_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6868_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6868_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6868_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation result:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\nThe context information mentions various film and documentary titles related to the assassination of John F. Kennedy, as well as a discussion about conspiracy theories and the government's release of documents related to the event. This suggests that the subject of John F. Kennedy is indeed associated with films or assassinations, making the triple correct according to the provided context information."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\n**Explanation:** The context information discusses various films and documentaries related to President John F. Kennedy's assassination, which supports the statement that the subject of John F. Kennedy has been filmmed (filmed) as assassinations."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "The information provided does not solely focus on filmmed assassinations of John F. Kennedy, but also includes various forms such as documentaries and television specials, as well as a videogame narrative, which broadens the scope beyond just filmed assassinations.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}